With Verizon Messages, keeping your conversations going has never been easier.
Let's go over some basic Verizon Messaging features to get you started.
Begin by tapping the Verizon Messages icon from any Home screen to open the app.
To send a text message, tap the Compose icon in the upper right hand corner of the screen.
Start typing the name or number of the person you want to send the message to and you'll
see matching contacts. Tap the one you want.
Addressing a message to more than one person
will start a group conversation.
To write your message, tap in the message
area and start typing.
When your message is complete, tap Send.
Responses to your text will be seen just below the message you sent.
To leave this conversation and see the list of all your conversations, tap the Back button.
When you get a new message from someone, their conversation jumps to the top of the list.
Tap the conversation to see the new message.
Then reply by tapping the text box and entering
your message. When done, tap Send.
When words just aren't enough, express yourself in pictures.
To add a picture to a message, simply tap the Plus button.
Then tap Picture. You can attach pictures that are already on your phone,
or take a new one to share.
Choose your photo and tap Attach.
Tap the text box to add a message to
go with your picture.
When your message is complete, tap Send.
For added creativity, Verizon Messages lets you create a postcard or add personal touches
to pictures using any combination of the collage, caption and sketch features.
You can create a collage with up to five pictures, add captions and choose your fonts, pinch
to resize and reposition, or use your fingers to sketch right on the image.
For more options, tap the Menu icon in the upper left.
You can scroll down to get Tips and Reminders and see What's New, like Integrated Messaging.
Integrated Messaging lets you send and receive messages on your tablet and computer, in addition
to your phone.
To see other useful features, tap Settings.
From here, you can personalize your conversations with different colors and font sizes, or set
up an Auto Reply to let people know you're busy when they text you.
These are just a few of the ways Verizon Messages makes texting easy and fun.
To learn more about Verizon Messages, please visit verizonwireless.com/verizonmessages