The Samsung Galaxy
S 5 from Verizon
has the KitKat Android
operating system
Watch this video to learn how
to get around your phone
To unlock your phone,
swipe in any direction
on the screen.
This is your Home screen.
Return to this screen at
any time by pressing
the Home key.
Swipe to the left to see
additional Home screens
where you can put apps
and shortcuts that
you use often.
The white indicators at the
bottom tell you which
of the 5 Home screens
you are currently viewing.
Swipe to the right
until you reach the
My Magazine Home screen.
My Magazine is a
personalized Home screen
based on your interests.
Swipe back to the left to
return to your traditional
Android Home screens.
The Favorites Tray below
the navigation indicators
lets you open frequently
used apps from
any Home screen.
Tap the Recent apps button
to open a list of recently
used apps for quick
multitasking.
Simply tap on an app
to open it.
Let us go back to the
Home screen.
Watch this video to
learn how to get
Touch the top of the screen
and slide your finger down
to open the Notification
Panel.
This panel shows you
notifications from apps,
missed calls or messages,
and more.
To clear a single notification,
swipe left or right.
Or to clear all notifications,
tap Clear.
Another thing you can do
on the Notification Panel is
quickly turn on or off
features like Bluetooth and
Location by tapping the
Settings shortcuts at the top.
You may need to respond
to prompts related to
your selection.
To jump to more settings,
in your Notification Panel,
tap the Settings icon near
the top right of the screen.
Here you can see all of
your phone settings.
Press the Home key to
return to the Home screen.
To explore your apps,
tap Apps.
In the upper right
corner you have
quick access to more options.
Tap the More options icon.
From here you can Edit the
order of your apps,
Uninstall downloaded apps,
change how you View the
apps, and more.
Tap the Back button to
close the menu and return
to the apps list.
Swipe to the left to find
the Play Store app.
Tap it to open the
Google Play Store,
where you can download
new apps, movies,
and more.
Spend time exploring your
new phone and in no time,
you will be an expert!