Set up your personal
and corporate email
quickly and efficiently
on your Samsung
Galaxy S 5 from Verizon.
Watch this video to learn how.
Begin by tapping Email.
Add your personal email
account by choosing an
account to set up from
the list of email providers.
Enter your Email address
and Password.
Tap Next.
When setup has finished,
select account options like
how far back your email is
synced to your phone
and tap Next.
You have the option to
give this account a name
on your phone.
Enter one if you choose.
Finally, enter your name to
show on outgoing messages.
You are done setting up
your personal email.
Tap Next to return
to the setup page.
If you have a Microsoft
Exchange account from your
work or school,
tap Corporate.
Enter your Email address
and Password.
Then be sure to tap
Manual setup.
Enter your Domain and
Exchange Server names.
Contact your organization
if you do not know
this information.
Tap next when complete.
Read the prompt and
tap OK if you agree.
An additional prompt may
require remote security.
Tap OK to continue.
Once on the Account
options page, change email
settings like sync options.
When finished tap Next.
Some accounts must be
able to remotely control
some security features
on your phone.
In order to allow a device
Administrator, tap Activate.
Finally, you have the option
to name the new account
on your phone.
Tap Next to complete setup.
Tap Done with accounts to
go to your email inbox.
to learn how.
Tap Done with accounts to
go to your email inbox.
To view all of your accounts
together, tap Inbox.
Then select Combined Inbox.
You are now done
setting up your email.
Enjoy the convenience of
having email on the go!