Talk with friends and
family using your
Samsung Galaxy S 5
from Verizon.
Watch this video
to learn how.
Begin by tapping Phone
from any Home screen.
With the keypad open,
enter the number
and tap the green call icon
to place a call.
During a call you can
Add someone else to the
call, open the Keypad,
use the Speaker,
mute the call,
or connect to
a Bluetooth headset.
Tap the End call icon
to end the call.
At the top of the phone app,
there are several tabs.
Recent displays a history of
Calls to and from the phone.
Your favorite contacts
appear in the Favorites tab
for quick access to contacts
you reach frequently.
Tap Contacts.
While in Contacts you can
quickly call any contact
just by swiping to the right.