Watch this video to learn
how to set up Wi-Fi and
Bluetooth on your Samsung
Galaxy S 5 from Verizon.
Open the Notification Panel
by touching and sliding
down from the top
of the screen.
Tap the Settings icon in
the upper right.
Then, tap Wi-Fi.
Make sure Wi-Fi is turned
on by sliding the Wi-Fi
switch to the right.
Wi-Fi will turn on and a
list of nearby Wi-Fi
networks will appear.
Tap the one you want
to connect to.
If you are connecting to a
secure network, you will
need to enter its password.
Once done, tap Connect.
You should now see
Connected underneath the
network name.
Now let us look at
connecting a Bluetooth
device to your phone.
Tap the back button to
return to Settings.
To set-up Bluetooth,
tap Bluetooth.
Make sure Bluetooth is
turned on by sliding the
Bluetooth switch to the right.
Bluetooth will turn on and
a list of nearby Bluetooth
devices will appear.
Please note that the device
you are attempting to pair
with must be in discovery
mode or the scan
will not find it.
Once you have found the
device you want to pair with,
select it.
You may need to confirm an
already existing password
for pairing.
If this is the case, tap OK.
On the phone, connected
devices will show under the
paired devices list.
Press the Home key
when complete.
To quickly turn Bluetooth
on and off, you can use the
Notification Panel by
touching and sliding your
finger down from the top
of the screen.
Then, tap Bluetooth.